#### Contact

astrunk87@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/alexstrunk (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Retail

Customer Service
Inventory Management

## Languages

English

# Alex Strunk

Fulfillment operations team lead

Greater Minneapolis-St. Paul Area

## Summary

An outgoing, passionate, and experienced leader who is growthmotivated. Excels in a fast-paced environment while maintaining detailed organization and communication. Values a fun, diverse, and dedicated team. Extensive experience in inventory management, managerial duties, supply and demand relations, and customer service.

Graduated from Augsburg University with a bachelor's degree in Communications with an emphasis on marketing.

## Experience

**Target** 

Team Lead

October 2021 - Present (2 years 2 months)

West Elm

Shipper/ Reciever

February 2020 - October 2021 (1 year 9 months)

Managed inventory by receiving weekly merchandise shipments, labeling and distributing products, and organizing all operational areas. Managed inter-organizational relations with local delivery hubs and national distribution centers to execute successful order deliveries.

**Papyrus** 

**Assistant Manager** 

February 2019 - February 2020 (1 year 1 month)

Greater Minneapolis-St. Paul Area

Performed managerial duties including financial responsibilities, leadership activities, and scheduling duties. Trained and coached employees on business standards and practices. Maintained and expanded guest relations. Frequently updated, organized and replenished inventory.

Marshalls
Frontend Coordinator
August 2016 - November 2017 (1 year 4 months)
Bloomington, Minnesota

Manage all frontend cashiers and employees. Resolved any technical and unforeseen issues involving frontend operations. Provided satisfactory customer service and resolutions of any customer issues. Managed men's apparel and merchandise inventory.

Elite6ops
Field Manager
July 2015 - August 2016 (1 year 2 months)
Bloomington, Minnesota

Managed facility operations such as repaired and updated equipment, managed weekly employee schedules, and managed payroll. Supervised and trained an extensive team of employees. Developed and managed company events. Resolved guest issues and developed positive customer relations.

## Target

Guest Services Manager August 2008 - August 2015 (7 years 1 month)

Managed an extensive volume of team members at any given time. Resolved guest issues while providing customer satisfaction. Coached and trained team members cashiering duties, inventory management, guest services, and product knowledge. Gained knowledge in other areas such as, photo development, assembly of exercise equipment, financial and office management, and order fulfillment.

Papyrus Key Holder March 2008 - November 2009 (1 year 9 months) Bloomington, Minnesota

Maintained and expanded guest relations. Performed managerial duties including financial responsibilities, leadership activities, and scheduling duties. Frequently updated, organized and replenished inventory.

ABX Air, Inc.
Package Handler
June 2007 - March 2008 (10 months)
Bloomington, Minnesota

Sorted and organized packages, as well as loaded and unloaded trucks.

## Education

Augsburg College

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), communications with marketing · (2009 - 2012)

Hamline University

· (2005 - 2006)